

Ebenezer Temitope Ogidiolu

Software Engineer

- +2349169442847
- www.ebendevlab.com
- No 1 Ewenla Street Lagos, Ewenla Street Lagos

Education

Software Enginering (Backend)

ALX Software Enginering School 2022 - 2023

Higher National Diploma (Computer Science)

Kogi State Polytechnic Lokoja 2011 - 2016

© Courses

Backend Web Dev. (Node JS)

Side-Hustle Internship Sep, 2022 - Oct, 2022

Skills

PHP & MySQL

Laravel

Wordpress

C# & VB.Net

HTML, CSS, JS

Android Dev

Graphics Design

₱ Language

English

Yoruba

Links

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ogidioluebenezer

https://www.github.com/dsoft02

https://www.ebendevlab.com

≪References

References available upon request

About Me

I'm a passionate and highly skilled software developer with expertise in backend technologies like Laravel, PHP, MySQL, and VB.net. I excel in database design, user interfaces, code writing, and problem-solving. My core strength is creating user-driven features and delivering results-aligned projects. I build strong stakeholder relationships and ensure effective communication.

Work Experience

O Sept. 2022- Present Syssoft Consultant Limited | Lagos, Nigeria

Software Application Developer

- Provide software solutions to insurance companies in Nigeria using PHP, MySQL, Javascript, and CSS programming languages.
- Developing digital financial reports and KPIs such as balance sheets, cash flow statements, income statements, and trail balances

Jan. 2018 – Dec. 2022 Ametech Global Solution System Ltd | Anyigba Kogi State, Nigeria

Part-Time Software Developer

- Developed Computer Based Test Website for Jamb Students
- Developed A time management software for Churches
- Developed Biometric Attendance software
- Development an Android Gospel Hymnbook App
- Developed An e-commerce / ads listing website

Oct. 2020 - Aug. 2022 United Bank for Africa Plc | Minna, Niger State, Nigeria

Relationship Officer

- Ensure deposit liability mobilization and account opening
- Ensure effective relationship management with new and existing customers
- Risk Asset appraisal, disbursement and Monitoring
- Optimally exploit new and existing opportunities in the market
- Ensure Zero tolerance for inactive/dormant accounts

Dec. 2019 – Sept. 2020 United Bank for Africa Plc | Minna, Niger State, Nigeria

Customer Service Officer

- Logging and resolution of customer issues and complaints
- Cross selling and promotion of the Bank's product and services to customers.
- Work with customer service manager to ensure proper customer service
- Always provide splendid customer services to customers in a friendly and courteous manner
- Open new bank accounts according to laid down rules and guidelines

Sept. 2017 – Nov. 2019 United Bank for Africa Plc | Anyigba, Kogi state, Nigeria

Bank Teller

- Provides account services to customers by receiving cash deposits and Payment of cash withdrawal on request and cashing of cheques.
- Cross selling of the Bank's product and services, Collection of E-Payment (Remitta, Paydirect, Western Union, Money Gram, e.t.c).
- ATM Custodians Team (loading of cash and basic ATM maintenance).